KYLE Z. CONDIE

(801) 599-9767 | kylecondie666@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/kyle-condie-6ba8111a1

GitHub: https://github.com/Frankenshtien | portfolio: https://frankenshtien.github.io/

SUMMARY

Full-stack web developer with strong experience in aesthetic design; fast learner that is excellent with time management and effective communication; works well under pressure and within strict time frames as a manager and individual contributor; enjoys bringing a dream design to reality, specifically in terms of functionality, and user interactivity

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Languages: JavaScript ES6+, Python, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL
- Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Insomnia, VS Code
- · Tools: Git, Express, Node, React, Handlebars, jQuery, Bootstrap, GraphQL, Jest, Redux, Sequelize, Mongoose

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

- Managed collaborative projects using Agile practices.
- Worked through the creative process of conceptualizing and building complete projects.
- Built fully functional backends and RESTful APIs.
- Designed and built fully functional SPA frontends using React.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate — University of Utah

OCT 2020 - MAY 2021

A 24-week intensive course focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars.js, and ReactJS.

PROJECTS

Landmark Tracker

This was my second group project and currently one of the things I'm most proud of. It allows you to create an account to post landmarks near you, and see landmarks other users have posted.

- Repo: https://github.com/gavin-asay/landmark-tracker
- Live: https://infinite-basin-15382.herokuapp.com/

OnlyMemes

This is my final group project from my boot camp, and the culmination of essentially everything I learned throughout it. The idea was essentially an exclusive meme viewing and sharing app with a paywall to access it. While the concept is a bit goofy, it was so much fun to make, and I learned a ton along the way.

- Repo: https://github.com/corycalaway/only_memes
- Live: https://onlymemes.herokuapp.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Salt Lake Barber Company — Barber Salt Lake City, UT | DEC 2018 - Present

Responsibilities: effectively communicating with clients to find their desired outcome; processing payments; educating clients on their specific needs

Curriculum — Barber Salt Lake City, UT | MAR 2015 - DEC 2018

Responsibilities: took artistic liberties to help clients feel comfortable and confident with themselves; educated clients on their specific needs and desired outcomes